# GREG BUNYEA

(in @gregbunyea

gregbunyea@gmail.com

**8**45-598-9455

## **PROFILE**

Experienced education technologist adept in evidencebased instruction, personalized online learning, and product development. I believe in growth through collaboration, and expanding access to education through digital tools. A techy by training, a communicator by nature, and a creator at heart.

#### **EDUCATION**

Carnegie Mellon University

2018 - 2019

M.S. of Education Technology (METALS)
METALS Merit Scholarship

University at Buffalo, SUNY

2014 - 2018

B.A. Computer Science, Studio Art Minor *Cum Laude*, Provost Scholarship

## **SELECTED EXPERIENCES**

Learning Engineer

2019 - present

Carnegie Mellon University, the Open Learning Initiative (OLI)

- Managing relationships with 3 domestic and 2 international clients, including SUNY OER Services
  - Awarded \$20,000 grant to collaborate with Swedish Royal Technical Institute (KTH)
- Support course product development through project management of diverse stakeholders, rapid onboarding & technical support, leading to course catalog expansion by 14%
- Create and lead key sessions in Learning Design track at annual week-long professional development intensive; organize additional in-person and remote training workshops throughout the year
- Collaborate on design of our next-gen platform via UX discussions, platform testing and issue triage to represent client, learning science and user experience perspectives

## Project Management Mentor, METALS Capstone

2020 - present

Carnegie Mellon University, Human-Computer Interaction Institute

- Manage Student-led project teams to complete multi-stage design challenge
- · Consult on client relationships, project development, and latest trends in education technology

# Project Coordinator, Consultant

Jan - Aug 2019

Renaissance Learning, Inc. (RL)

- · Led cross-functional team of 5 to design dashboard for intra/inter-district data comparison
- Coordinated 37 stakeholders for research, analysis, and user-testing sessions of dashboard designs
- · Drove development, testing and iteration cycles with Agile sprints, issue triage and design reviews

## Lead Teaching Assistant

2016 - 2018

University at Buffalo SUNY, Dept of Computer Science

- · Developed content structure and format for instruction to 660 students in a flipped classroom setting
- Designed novel online learning platform to connect student-created videos to key topic areas
- Coordinated delivery of content with approximately 40 TAs and Faculty on weekly basis

## **TECH**

Learning Design: Canvas LMS, CMU's OpenSimon Toolkit, Coursetune

Content Creation: Adobe Suite, Canva, OpenStudio, Audacity, Inkscape, Krita, Unity, Godot

**Productivity:** Trello, ZohoCRM, Miro, GoogleSuite, FreshDesk **Programming:** Python, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, processing